Preliminary Guide to The Thomas Hahn Chesapeake and Ohio Canal collection, 1939-1993 MS2020
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Lock 38., 1970 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 285)
- Canal boat on Canal. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 286)
- Canal boat on Canal. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 287)
- Canal boat on Canal. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 288)
- Bridge. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 289)
- House. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 290)
- House. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 291)
- House. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 292)
- Lock 23 and Inlet Lock., 1938-1939 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 293)
- Great Falls Tavern., 1938-1939 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 294)
- Lock House and Lock. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 295)
- Canal boat. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 296)
- Canal boat. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 297)
- Lock. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 298)
- House at Lock 7. Settlement cracks in the wall, carelessly built after the 1936 flood tore away some of it. Dormer windows and plumbing added 1936-1939 and interior rearranged. NPS Restoration. (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 299)
- House at Lock 5 (gone)., 1938-1939 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 300)
- House at Lock 5 (gone)., 1938-1939 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 301)
- Inside of canal boat. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 302)
- House. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 303)
- Great Falls Tavern., 1938-1939 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 304)
- House. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 305)
- Houses. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 306)
- Part of a house. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 307)
- Great Falls Tavern., 1938-1939 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 308)
- Great Falls Tavern., 1938-1939 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 309)
- House. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 310)
- Great Falls Tavern., 1938-1939 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 311)
- Lock House and Lock. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 312)
- House at Lock 16., 1938-1939 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 313)
- House at Lock 12. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 314)
- House at Lock 10. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 315)
- Canal masonry. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 316)
- House at Lock 9. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 317)
- House at Lock 8 framed by maple trees. NPS Restoration., 1939 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 318)
- Dick Hanes, Captain of Boat, no. 20. Point of Rocks, MD. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 319)
- John W. Ault, Lock Tender at Two Locks Above Harpers Ferry. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 320)
- Potomac Canal Boundary Marker near (1/4 mile above) Magazine Lock (Lock 6). 40' from river bank. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 321)
- Man with model of canal barge. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 322)
- Georgetown Incline. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 323)
- Monocacy Aqueduct. February, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 324)
- Monocacy Aqueduct. February, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 325)
- Monocacy Aqueduct. February, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 326)
- Monocacy Aqueduct. February, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 327)
- Building on masonry. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 328)
- Building on masonry. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 329)
- J.P. Mose, Boatman C&O Canal. December, 1982 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 330)
- The railroad Lift Bridge at Williamsport, MD. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 331)
- Canal. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 332)
- Lock. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 333)
- Dam. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 334)
- Old Dredge and barge between Chain Bridge and Lock 5., 1939 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 335)
- Lewis Henry Crass (Buggs). Catactin Lock #29. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 336)
- Barge., 1920 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 337)
- Riders on a canal boat, C&O Canal, August 26, 1916 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 338)
- Point of Rocks. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 339)
- House., 1972 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 340)
- House in flood. January, 1973 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 341)
- Lock House on berm. Lock tender operated Locks 47 and 48., 1974 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 342)
- Wooden building. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 343)
- Lock House at Lock #51. March, 1974 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 344)
- Lock House at Lock #57. March 25, 1974 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 345)
- South Portal of Raw Paw Tunnel. July, 9, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 346)
- Harpers Ferry. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 347)
- House of Lock 43., 1939 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 348)
- Lock House 29. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 349)
- Wooden House. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 350)
- House. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 351)
- C&O Canal near Great Falls. Erosion of towpath below Lock #19. March 30, 1936 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 352)
- Great Falls Tavern and Lock 20. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 353)
- Canal. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 354)
- Lock Keeper, 1920 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 355)
- Lock House 70., 1992 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 356)
- Lock House 72., 1992 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 357)
- Lock House 70., 1992 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 358)
- Skating at the Abner Cloud House on the C&O Canal by Earl Minderman. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 359)
- Image of barge on canal and train on bridge. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 360)
- Lock #43., 1939 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 361)
- Lock #42., 1939 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 362)
- Lock #74. Middle Lock at the Narrows, Milepost 175.47. Historical photo 11004-21-G, Coal Co. Records, CA. Not drop gate at upper end of lock, 1900-1920 (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 363)
- Stone structure. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 364)
- Stone structure. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 365)
- Stone structure. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 366)
- Stone structure. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 367)
- Stone structure. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 368)
- Ranger and group. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 369)
- Stone structure. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 370)
- Stone structure next to canal. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 371)
- Stone structure. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 372)
- Northwest corner of forge. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 373)
- Ranger and group. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 374)
- Ranger and group. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 375)
- Family and modern building. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 376)
- People and modern building. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 377)
- Great Falls. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 378)
- Children among rocks. n.d, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 379)
- Waterway. n.d., undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 380)
- C&O Canal Hike (36 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 1)
- Georgetown (21 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 2)
- Tide Lock (52 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 3)
- Lock #5 (16 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 4)
- Chain Bridge (9 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 5)
- Lock #1 (6 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 6)
- Lock #2 (4 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 7)
- Lock #3 (6 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 8)
- Lock #4 (13 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 9)
- Lock #6 (47 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 10)
- Lock #7 (11 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 11)
- Lock #8 (8 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 12)
- Lock #9 (5 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 13)
- Lock #10 (5 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 44)
- Lock #11 (11 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 14)
- Lock #12 (11 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 15)
- Lock #13 (5 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 16)
- Lock #14 (11 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 17)
- Widewater (5 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 18)
- Lock #15 (12 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 19)
- Lock #16 (8 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 20)
- Stop gate (3 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 21)
- Lock #17 (3 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 22)
- Lock #18 (15 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 23)
- Lock #19 (1 picture), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 24)
- Great Falls (15 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 25)
- Swains Lock #21 (5 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 26)
- Lock #22 (9 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 27)
- Lock #23 (6 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 28)
- Seneca Levels (44 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 29)
- Lock #25 (9 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 30)
- Whites Ferry (13 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 31)
- Monocay Aqueduct (10 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 32)
- Point of Rocks (15 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 33)
- Lock #28 (11 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 34)
- Lock #29 (16 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 35)
- Catoctin Aqueduct (3 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 36)
- Brunswick (22 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 37)
- Lock #32 (10 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 38)
- Harpers Ferry (9 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 39)
- Lock #34 (5 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 40)
- Dam #3 (6 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 41)
- Lock #35 (8 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 42)
- Lock #36 (14 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 22, Folder 43)
- Lock #37 (16 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 1)
- Antietam Village (10 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 2)
- Shepherdstown River Lock (1 picture), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 3)
- Shepherdstown (27 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 4)
- Lock #39 (16 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 5)
- Lock #40 (7 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 6)
- Taylors Landing (6 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 7)
- Dam #4 (21 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 8)
- Lock #42 (5 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 9)
- Lock #43 (17 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 10)
- Williamsport (16 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 11)
- Dam #5 (15 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 12)
- Cliff Above Dam #5 (5 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 13)
- Lock #45 (9 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 14)
- Conococheague Aqueduct (28 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 15)
- Charles Mill (9 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 16)
- Four Locks (33 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 17)
- Big Pool (5 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 18)
- Licking Creek Aqueduct (13 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 19)
- Lock #51 (1 picture), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 20)
- Lock #52 (9 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 21)
- Tonoloway Aqueduct (9 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 22)
- Hancock (22 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 23)
- Devil's Eyebrow (5 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 24)
- Lock #53 (12 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 25)
- Lock #54 (6 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 26)
- Lock #55 (20 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 27)
- Lock #56 (2 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 28)
- Lock #57 (2 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 29)
- Tonoloway Aqueduct (2 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 30)
- Lock #58 (3 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 31)
- Lock #59 (7 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 32)
- Lock #60 (3 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 33)
- Lock #61 (1 picture), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 34)
- Lock #62 (4 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 35)
- Lock #63 1/3 (4 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 36)
- Lock #64 2/3 (6 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 37)
- Lock #66 (4 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 38)
- Paw Paw Tunnel (18 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 39)
- Lock #67 (1 picture), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 40)
- Lock #68 (6 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 41)
- Lock #71 (9 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 42)
- Lock #74 (2 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 43)
- Lock #75 (6 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 44)
- Evitts Creek Aqueduct (33 pictures), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 45)
- Lock #72 (5 picture), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 46)
- Lock #73 (1 picture), undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 23, Folder 47)
- Aqueduct Bridge footings looking toward Georgetown, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Canal Clipper, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
- C&O Canal boats, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
- C&O Canal boats, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Slide unknown, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
- C&O Canal above Georgetown with boats backed up, Potomac Aqueduct for Alexandria Canal in background, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
- C&O Canal above Georgetown, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
- C&O Canal Georgetown Location of inclined ramp and entrance basin, undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
- C&O Canal Old Stone House at Fletchers, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Abner Cloud House (Fletchers), undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Group with brooms, undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Canoes on the C&O Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Underpass at Fletchers, undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
- C&O Canal with buildings, undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Potomac River, undated (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Canoe on the C&O Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 16)
- C&O Canal Ft. Frederick (State Park) DEM, 1938 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Canal Clipper on the C&O Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Great Falls VA Moses Brown Mill Pautucket, RI Early Factory Am Heritage Encycl Am History 5:380, undated (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Canal Clipper on C&O Canal with building in background, undated (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Lock #5, undated (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Canal Clipper on C&O Canal at a lock, undated (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Control gate on Feeden Canal at Lock 5, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- House at Lock 5 15A, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- House at Lock 5 15A, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- C&O Canal Lock 6 drained November, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 26)
- Canal Clipper on the C&O Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 27)
- Rear view of house at Lock 5 15B, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Control gate on Feeden Canal at Lock 5 11-1, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 29)
- Portrait of George Washington, undated (Box 24, Folder 30)
- #6, 1942 (Box 24, Folder 31)
- December, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 32)
- 981-C&O Canal Tow path south of Tunnel DEM, 1938 (Box 24, Folder 33)
- Lock keeper's house Lock #6 C&O Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 34)
- Rear view of house at Lock 6 17A, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 35)
- Typical C&O Barge, undated (Box 24, Folder 36)
- Lock keeper's house Lock #75. This is last lift lock Washington DC 175 miles, undated (Box 24, Folder 37)
- Calligraphy Masonry Principal Story Attic Story, undated (Box 24, Folder 38)
- Canal Clipper approaching Lock 6 from downstream L-3227-119 DEM September, 1942 (Box 24, Folder 39)
- Canoe on C&O Canal with Great Falls Tavern in the background, undated (Box 24, Folder 40)
- #7, 1940 (Box 24, Folder 41)
- 1416- C&O Canal Pkwy Wisc. Ave. Bridge fr. Towpath. DEM, 1940 (Box 24, Folder 42)
- Stone Pier C&O Canal Aqueduct in Potomac R. 55 L-3233-:5, undated (Box 24, Folder 43)
- 1940 (Box 24, Folder 44)
- C&O Canal in Georgetown, undated (Box 24, Folder 45)
- C&O Canal Company seal, undated (Box 24, Folder 46)
- C&O Canal Watergate Tide Lock, undated (Box 24, Folder 47)
- Lock 3 and 4 Winter, undated (Box 24, Folder 48)
- C&O Canal Company letterhead scene, undated (Box 24, Folder 49)
- Lock 16 (obverse) C&O Canal Company seal (reverse), undated (Box 24, Folder 50)
- C&O Canal at Georgetown, undated (Box 24, Folder 51)
- 1023 C&O Canal dedication old timers, Sylvester Pennyfield & C. Stewart DEM, undated (Box 24, Folder 52)
- Marching band in Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 53)
- Georgetown Harbor, undated (Box 24, Folder 54)
- C&O Canal in Georgetown, undated (Box 24, Folder 55)
- Mule and people, undated (Box 24, Folder 56)
- Georgetown Harbor, undated (Box 24, Folder 57)
- Key Bridge - C&O Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 58)
- Tidelock, Potomac River, C&O Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 59)
- Lock in Georgetown October, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 60)
- Key Bridge viewed from downstream; note floodwaters. NSP WDC, 08/20/1955 (Box 24, Folder 61)
- Wisconsin Avenue, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 62)
- High Street (Wisconsin Avenue) Bridge Georgetown C&O Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 63)
- C&O Canal Marker Maryland State Agents, undated (Box 24, Folder 64)
- C&O Canal Marker C&O Canal Company, 1850 (Box 24, Folder 65)
- C&O Canal in Georgetown, undated (Box 24, Folder 66)
- C&O Canal in Georgetown, undated (Box 24, Folder 67)
- C&O Canal in Georgetown, undated (Box 24, Folder 68)
- C&O Canal in Georgetown, undated (Box 24, Folder 69)
- C&O Canal Pkwy. Old houses along towpath in Georgetown, undated (Box 24, Folder 70)
- C&O Canal as graph, undated (Box 24, Folder 71)
- Boat on water, undated (Box 24, Folder 72)
- Washington Aqueduct Bridge at Rock Creek, undated (Box 24, Folder 73)
- Rock Creek and canal in ice, with passenger or "packet" boat on the water going beneath the M Street bridge., ca. 1905 (Box 24, Folder 74)
- High Street (Wisconsin Ave.) over the Chesapeake and Ohio Canal. Vigilant Firehouse (1825). Photo by: Robert G. Johnsson, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 75)
- Godey Lime Plant Washington, DC Rock Creek (C&O Canal), undated (Box 24, Folder 76)
- Pair of cast-iron pipe arches under construction across Rock Creek with a packet boat in the foreground. Officially called the Washington Aqueduct Bridge No. 6, this structure would later be incorporated into what is today the Pennsylvania Avenue Bridge., ca. 1860 (Box 24, Folder 77)
- C&O Canal towpath crossover Georgetown, undated (Box 24, Folder 78)
- C&O Canal Company Seal (reverse) Lock 16 (obverse), undated (Box 24, Folder 79)
- Mule stables on Rock Creek C&O Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 80)
- Patowmack Company 1803 seal, undated (Box 24, Folder 81)
- Patowmack Company 1803 seal, undated (Box 24, Folder 82)
- Inspecting (Bruce McHenry) valve of old lock gate; lock 72; Chesapeake and Ohio Canal, Maryland photo by: Robert G. Johnsson, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 83)
- Upstream (south) Portal of Paw Paw Tunnel, undated (Box 24, Folder 84)
- Downstream view of house at Lock 7 (Glen Echo), 1939 (Box 24, Folder 85)
- House at Lock 8, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 86)
- Lock and house on the C&O Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 87)
- Lock on the C&O Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 88)
- House on the C&O Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 89)
- House at Lock 9, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 90)
- C&O Canal: Barge model stern view, port side March 23, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 91)
- Upstream view of house at Lock 10, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 92)
- Upstream view of lock 10, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 93)
- 982-C&O Canal at Pawpaw Tunnel (Looking toward So., undated (Box 24, Folder 94)
- Rocky Run culvert below Lock 11, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 95)
- House at Lock 11, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 96)
- Waterway, undated (Box 24, Folder 97)
- House at Lock 13, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 98)
- House at Lock 14, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 99)
- Field, undated (Box 24, Folder 100)
- C&O Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 101)
- C&O Canal Lock 16 Lock house, undated (Box 24, Folder 102)
- Mile Marker 9 miles to WC, undated (Box 24, Folder 103)
- Waterway, undated (Box 24, Folder 104)
- House at Lock 17, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 105)
- Canal Repair Wide Water L-3227-134, undated (Box 24, Folder 106)
- Field L3233-25, undated (Box 24, Folder 107)
- C&O Canal Lock near Wide Water, undated (Box 24, Folder 108)
- Stop lock above Lock 16, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 109)
- House at Lock 18, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 110)
- House at Lock 16, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 111)
- Inlet culvert at Lock 17, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 112)
- Waterway, undated (Box 24, Folder 113)
- Lock 18 Sept, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 114)
- Log house south of Tavern at Great Falls about 1884, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 115)
- Great Falls Tavern from the southwest, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 116)
- 1396 - C&O Canal Pkwy Boating on canal above Great Falls, undated (Box 24, Folder 117)
- Great Falls Tavern from landward side. NCP 746 WDC August 24, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 118)
- East side of Great Falls Tavern. Wooden kitchen added 1926, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 119)
- Great Falls Tavern (1828), 1939 (Box 24, Folder 120)
- Frame house #1 at Great Falls, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 121)
- Log house, frame houses #1 and #2 at Great Falls (1884), undated (Box 24, Folder 122)
- Frame house #2 at Great Falls, downstream view, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 123)
- Flooded waterway, undated (Box 24, Folder 124)
- House at Swains Lock (No. 21), 1939 (Box 24, Folder 125)
- Building next to C&O Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 126)
- North front of Great Falls Tavern (1832), 1939 (Box 24, Folder 127)
- C&O Canal: Lock 20 and Great Falls Tavern WDC September 18, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 128)
- Log House at Lock 23 (violets) built on foundation of lock house, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 129)
- G.F. md. autumn scene, undated (Box 24, Folder 130)
- Great Falls Tavern and Lock winter scene, undated (Box 24, Folder 131)
- Canal scene, undated (Box 24, Folder 132)
- G.F. Tavern named "Crommelin House", undated (Box 24, Folder 133)
- Seneca Aqueduct (No. 1), 1939 (Box 24, Folder 134)
- Swinging bridge at Edwards Ferry (Lock 25), 1939 (Box 24, Folder 135)
- Bridge or aqueduct, undated (Box 24, Folder 136)
- Bridge or aqueduct, undated (Box 24, Folder 137)
- Lock on C&O Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 138)
- The Trojan and C&O Canal at Sandy Hook, undated (Box 24, Folder 139)
- Winch house and stop lock at Dam no. 4, undated (Box 24, Folder 140)
- Canal Boat, undated (Box 24, Folder 141)
- Lock #12 and lockkeepers house C&O Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 142)
- Aqueduct, undated (Box 24, Folder 143)
- Aqueduct, undated (Box 24, Folder 144)
- Aqueduct or Bridge, undated (Box 24, Folder 145)